{
    "subject": "resource/The_Gambler_(2014_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_crime_drama_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film 'The Gambler' (2014) is American crime drama films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9745346307754517,
            "question": "Is 'The Gambler' (2014) a crime drama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9067991971969604,
            "question": "What is the subject of the film 'The Gambler' (2014) according to the given information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7676632404327393,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Gambler' (2014)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.747840404510498,
            "question": "Is the film 'The Gambler' (2014) a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6574264764785767,
            "question": "What type of films does 'The Gambler' (2014) belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6424700617790222,
            "question": "Give an example of a film genre that 'The Gambler' (2014) falls under."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5705997943878174,
            "question": "Can you describe the typical themes explored in American crime drama films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549875497817993,
            "question": "What type of stories are typically found in American crime drama films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5369045734405518,
            "question": "To what category do American crime drama films belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4878573715686798,
            "question": "What can you infer about the plot of 'The Gambler' (2014) based on its genre?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film 'The Gambler' (2014) is American crime drama films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6233_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what category do American crime drama films belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6233_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of stories are typically found in American crime drama films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6233_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the typical themes explored in American crime drama films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6233_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6233_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context information, the subject of the film 'The Gambler' (2014) is a literature professor with a gambling problem, not an American crime drama film. The triple statement does not match the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: All the provided documents describe \"The Gambler\" as an American crime drama film, thus supporting the statement that the subject of the film 'The Gambler' (2014) is American crime drama films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The subject of the film 'The Gambler' (2014) is not exclusively American crime drama films. It falls under a wider category of Drama, specifically Crime-Thriller, due to its narrative focusing on a gambling problem and the character's encounters with gangsters.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the film \"The Gambler\" (2014) is described as a crime-thriller drama movie, which indicates that its subject matter involves elements of both thriller and drama genres, not solely American crime drama films.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}